{"instructions": ["You will be listening to two sound beeps, one of which has fluctuations. <p></p>Your task is to click on either <strong>first</strong> or <strong>second</strong> to indicate in which sound beep you heard the fluctuation.", "When you are ready, click <strong>Continue</strong>."], "feedback": true, "holdfeedback": false, "feedbackdur": 600, "serveraudio": false, "estimatedduration": 4, "randomize": false, "isi": 600, "volume": [{"plugin": "html-button-response", "prompt": "To begin, make sure you are in a quiet room and wearing your <strong>wired</strong> head/earphones. Let us adjust the volume before starting the test.<p> Click <strong>Continue</strong> to proceed.</p>", "choices": ["Continue"]}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Now adjust your computer volume up to a comfortable (but not too loud) level.", "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/BinauralFM/demo/volume.wav", "choices": ["I have adjusted the volume, let's continue"]}, {"plugin": "html-button-response", "prompt": "The headphones are usually marked as left/right to indicate which ear they are for. Did you make sure the right headphone is in your right ear, and the left headphone is in your left ear? It is very important for making the correct decisions.", "choices": ["Yes, let's continue."]}], "trials": [{"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Which one had the fluctuation?", "choices": ["first", "second"], "answer": 1, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/BinauralFM/demo/3.2Hz_1_ur5yxKemSJm0AHGl.wav", "cond": 1, "annot": {"fdev": "3.2Hz"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Which one had the fluctuation?", "choices": ["first", "second"], "answer": 1, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/BinauralFM/demo/3.2Hz_1_bAINcSkKLVd0xyuI.wav", "cond": 1, "annot": {"fdev": "3.2Hz"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Which one had the fluctuation?", "choices": ["first", "second"], "answer": 1, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/BinauralFM/demo/3.2Hz_1_vNP96vl5rI4fpAJ3.wav", "cond": 1, "annot": {"fdev": "3.2Hz"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Which one had the fluctuation?", "choices": ["first", "second"], "answer": 2, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/BinauralFM/demo/3.2Hz_2_AWGuAS43ih3OcF3x.wav", "cond": 1, "annot": {"fdev": "3.2Hz"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Which one had the fluctuation?", "choices": ["first", "second"], "answer": 1, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/BinauralFM/demo/3.2Hz_1_mxKqMXgTOD5fLocJ.wav", "cond": 1, "annot": {"fdev": "3.2Hz"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Which one had the fluctuation?", "choices": ["first", "second"], "answer": 2, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/BinauralFM/demo/3.2Hz_2_0mMkrbR7UUHrpr7o.wav", "cond": 1, "annot": {"fdev": "3.2Hz"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Which one had the fluctuation?", "choices": ["first", "second"], "answer": 1, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/BinauralFM/demo/3.2Hz_1_AixXY4HYRcjopkor.wav", "cond": 1, "annot": {"fdev": "3.2Hz"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Which one had the fluctuation?", "choices": ["first", "second"], "answer": 1, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/BinauralFM/demo/3.2Hz_1_szsUwhMwwe1Ce4rM.wav", "cond": 1, "annot": {"fdev": "3.2Hz"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Which one had the fluctuation?", "choices": ["first", "second"], "answer": 1, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/BinauralFM/demo/3.2Hz_1_7PH1IbDYTJaSBOUX.wav", "cond": 1, "annot": {"fdev": "3.2Hz"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Which one had the fluctuation?", "choices": ["first", "second"], "answer": 2, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/BinauralFM/demo/3.2Hz_2_JepiIHe9ptscGpz6.wav", "cond": 1, "annot": {"fdev": "3.2Hz"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Which one had the fluctuation?", "choices": ["first", "second"], "answer": 1, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/BinauralFM/demo/3.2Hz_1_KwSGqE1Smjw1QNie.wav", "cond": 1, "annot": {"fdev": "3.2Hz"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Which one had the fluctuation?", "choices": ["first", "second"], "answer": 1, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/BinauralFM/demo/3.2Hz_1_ECFqo34LwLP3fHAM.wav", "cond": 1, "annot": {"fdev": "3.2Hz"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Which one had the fluctuation?", "choices": ["first", "second"], "answer": 1, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/BinauralFM/demo/3.2Hz_1_gaduWuM9OHoT31LO.wav", "cond": 1, "annot": {"fdev": "3.2Hz"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Which one had the fluctuation?", "choices": ["first", "second"], "answer": 1, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/BinauralFM/demo/3.2Hz_1_rNsMc9mLvSbe5fuG.wav", "cond": 1, "annot": {"fdev": "3.2Hz"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Which one had the fluctuation?", "choices": ["first", "second"], "answer": 2, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/BinauralFM/demo/3.2Hz_2_WG5jzrLcdugkxcRN.wav", "cond": 1, "annot": {"fdev": "3.2Hz"}}]}